Extend
te wo nobashite Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut thro Ed to fear
wo kirisaite Cut through the wind, and persevere
chizu wo egaite yuke Chart your own course. the time to push forward is here
cha ni Video Editing Graphics fedew Datenshi In a time like a storm, hear the tidal waves roar,
dai Soundtracking Timing Halee Gab Pollychan we keep trudging along but we're still wanting more
Kizuk Gab Pollychan But in spite of it all more
ta kachikan sae mo Quality Control Gab Pepperjack Galaxy 9000 Westfal Zenef Gol D. Rocks But in spite of it all, the foundation we built
Quality Control Gab Pepperjack Galaxy 9000 Westfal Gol D. Rocks Zenef for ourselves was about to fall
no ka douka nante Subtitle Editing Gol D. Rocks Gordingus Pollychan Zenef Who to ask? As if there's anyone listening
inda Typesetting FiberAhmed Gab Pollychan guess you'll never be one hundred percent sure
de Translation Crunchyroll Liisa-Pekka But if you shut your eyes to the chaos.
and
tojireba and you'd only take a breath
Ukab When you ope
wa When you open up your eyes
chi you will find where you were meant to be
Exten
te wo nobashite Extend your hand, no need to fear
Cut thro need to fear
risaite Cut through the wind, and persevere
Kura Kick out the d
wo kettobashite Kick out the dark until the sky clears
Ima Even as we ac
doing wn best interests.
darou doing what we each believe is for our own
Chart your
t your own course, the time to push forward is here
C 11
SMEPAC
SNEPAGE
I don't believe it!
< Mt. Atama Thieves, Leader of the Ashura Doji The Oniwabanshu captains.
< h Y Leader of the Mt Atama Thieves, Ashura Doji and the Mimawari-gumi's, too...
2 < h Leader of thel Mt. Atama Thieves, Ashura Doji Most of them are down!
Daikoku!
Lord Kazekage!
Captain Hotei!
So that's what the legendary yakuza is capable of. huh?!
He resisted the effects of the ice ogre. but still took advantage of its power!
I think I'm beginning to understand...
why Wano has been so feared..
Boss!
Boss Hyogoro!
What are you waiting for. Yatappe?!
Empty your mind!
If I turn into an ice ogre...
1 know!
Just give me a second!
I'm gonna do it!
I'll do it right now!
Of course it's difficult...
After all, that man...
is like a father to us!
Tsunagoro, cut me down right now!
Boss Hyogoro...
I'll join you soon!
Omasa!
Dammit!
Isn't there any way you can finish in time, Mr. Tanuki?!
I can't fight it anymore, either!
There's no saving me now!
Just do it!
Don't let me...
Boss Omasa!
Don't let me hurt you all!
Mr. Tanuki!
Surely the cure is ready by now?!
The entire floor...
all of our companions...
will succumb to the ice ogre once more!
Your Awesomeness!
We work for you, man... Why do we have to die from your virus, too?!
Shut your mouths, you lowlifes!
You punks have outlived your usefulness!
Listen up!
If I can't use you, you're as good as trash!
The ice ogre virus is my crowning achievement!
If anything. it was made especially for you!
Hey. Pleasures!
You guys already lost the ability lottery!
Now you're nothing but cackling cannon fodder!
Th-That's awful!
Hey, Waiters!
You can wait all you like, but there're no more smile fruits coming!
You guys lost your chance to be somebody!
The Eternal Waiters.
It's a fitting name. since all you can do is wait!
The only way you layabouts can be of use to the mighty Beast Pirates...
is by at least becoming an ogre before you die.
That way you can do something worth a damn with your final moments!
So are you saying... we should just die?!
Oh! Now you get it!
(-)
We already have plenty of troops.
What an awful thing to say!
No way...
You had your chance!
Those antibodies could still save some of you!
Dammit! I'm not gonna die without a fight!
Cut down every ice ogre. samurai and allies alike!
Now that's what I'm talkin' about!
111 Fight your asses off to survive!
16 His treatment of his men is sickening!
Indeed it is.
Hey. you damn samurai!
Maybe you don't-realize who you're protecting over there.
but in case you forgot, that tanuki...
is a pirate, just like us!
Queen...
Synthesizing that many antibodies in such a short amount of time?!
Don't make me laugh!
He probably just gave himself the cure and bailed!
He's nothing like you villains!
Are you sure about that?
Pirates aren't known for being loyal!
Boss Hyogoro!
I'll be right behind you!
Don't be so hasty to follow me...
Big Boss! Big Boss!
Farewell...
Wait!
Don't try and stop me, Mr. Tanuki!
We have no other choice!
Just wait!
I'll save him right now!
Boss! Swallow it!
Thank goodness! We made it just in time!
B-BosS...
Alright! It's working!
Your body is warming up!
**
Boss Hyogoro!
Are you all right?!
Yeah...
It worked!
I knew you could do it, Mr. Tanuki!
Miyagi! Tristan! On the double!
Right away. Dr. Chopper!
What's that?
It's all set. Dr. Chopper!
Alright! Let's do it!
Dr. Chopper! Just give the order!
- A cannon?! - A cannon?!
Chopperphage.
N E Nebulizer!
N B
Fire!
Everyone! Inhale the mist!
What do you think you're doing. you damn tanuki?!
The pinnacle of my work... What have you done!?
Individually handing out medicine to thousands of soldiers would be impossible!
So I created my own virus using the antibodies!
You what?!
A good virus can counteract a bad virus!
This way, everyone just needs to breathe in the mist to be cured!
You're just some ship doctor from a backwater pirate crew..
Where did you learn something like this?!
We scattered all over the world to train for moments like this!
You even cured my own guys of ice ogre!
What gives you the right?!
Who in their right mind would use a virus as a weapon?!
There's no way to control if!
I am not gonna be lectured on ethics by a damn tanuki!
Who the hell do you take me for?!
C 11,
Pleasures?!
Why?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Stay out of this: you rats!
Up yours. Queen!
You nearly killed our brothers..
but Mr. Tanuki here saved our asses!
We'd rather die side-by-side with the guy who saved usS...
instead of being killed by our crazy-ass boss!
Ain't that right. boys?!
Thank you, tanuki!
We are in your debt. Mr. Tanuki!
Mr. Tanuki... Thank you!
ou're really somethin' else. little tanuki.
- Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! - Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! - Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! - Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki!
Go to hell, Queen!
You little shits!
What the hell is this?!
Not bad at all, tanuki!
Now let him have it.
Thanks, Marco!
There's just one more thing that I wanna say!
Tanuki!
0 0
Rumble!
Monster Point!
You got this! - Get him! - Get him!
What?!
I'm not a tanuki!
We're so sorry! We're so sorry! 're so sorry! We're so sor 're so sorry! We're so sori I'm not a tanuki! We're'so sorry! We're so sorry!
Right-BrainTower Inside the Dome
There's a bunch of space between each floor of the castle!
No one'll see us there!
Okay!
Lord Momonosuke! Please hold on just a little longer!
Momonosuke, are you okay?
I am not okay...
I 111
What do you mean?!
111 =/11
I am not okay. I feel awful.
I hate myself.
Everyone gives me too much credit!
I am frivolous, stupid...
weak, foolish, and I make myself sick..
Lord Momonosuke, I think you're amazing!
I am not amazing at all!
Even if you're small now.
I know that you'll grow up to be a proper shogun one day!
You'll be an even greater man than Kozuki Oden ever was!
I am not... I am not...
am not amazing at all!
What?!
// An eel?!
Lord Momonosuke!
Why do you look like that?
This is what happens to Lord Momonosuke when his emotions run high.
Huh?
Did you eat a devil fruit or something?
Indeed, I did...
Guest Parlor Inside the Castle
Speaking of Kaido...
Back when the Marines had him held captive...
Vegapunk extracted Kaido's hereditary elements...
and used them to create an artificial devil fruit.
The government requested that he hand over the fruit.
but since Vegapunk considered it a disappointing failure.
it was stored at Punk Hazard long term.
Why bring that up now?
Punk Hazard was blown up.
The fruit should be gone now.
I can only hope it was destroyed in that explosion.
but Marine Branch G-5 reported that one facility was still in operation...
I'm just grateful..o that it was a failure.
"Treasury"
Who treated our wounds?
I do not know...
But I believe I may have seen someone...
No, it must have been a dream...
After all, it could not have been...
Sir Luffy and his allies are engaging Kaido in our stead.
We should not stay here and sit idly by!
The battle for this island rages on!
Let us move!
We still have life left to give!
You guys!
You look like hell!
How Ive missed you all!
You're so much older now!
L-Lord Oden!
It's no wonder you're surprised!
Toki sent me here to the future with the help of her ability!
I'll explain everything later.
It's a long story!
Lord Oden!
So that is why you are here!
Sorry for being late!
But we don't have time to catch up right now!
Now come!
We go to Kaido, the man we failed to kill on that fateful day!
Of course!
We are with you!
That has been our wish from the beginning!
Let us depart!
I knew you guys would say that!
Hold it. everyone!
There's no way he's alive!
He must be an impostor!
What are you saying. Ashura?!
Kin'emon!
Remember Lady Toki's words!
Travel to the past is impossible...
but one can leap ahead to the future.
"Travel to the past is impossible"!
Lady Toki's ability was to send people to the future!
Lord Oden died that day!
That fact would not change. even in the future!
No one can change the past!
But... it could be him!
I get that!
But..!
Snap out of it, Kin'emon!
Look!
He doesn't even bleed!
Impossible!
Ashura...
I thought you had pledged to be my samurai.
Be my samurai!
Ashura!
Now you can see his true colors...
I know we all feel the same...
I wish he were real as well...
But... this is an impostor!
How terrible!
Who could be posing as Lord Oden?!
It's not really him?!
Dammit!
Are you okay. Ashura?!
But... his demeanor...
It is exactly like Oden's!
The only one who could mimic him so perfectly..
is one of us!
So it's you!
Kanjuro!
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
Ashura, forgive me!
This is my fault!
If I hadn't failed to finish off Kanjuro...
Even the sharpest blade dulls when turned on a friend...
It must have been so hard on you...
Is this a painting? Where is your real body?!
I am puppeteering Oden from afar!
It's quite the exhausting task!
Hey, Kiku!
Your blade indeed found its mark!
I am gravely wounded, as well!
I expect this will be my final act!
But the one thing that keeps me pressing forward..
is my grudge toward the Kozuki!
Therefore, before I pass away...
I will pierce through the heart of the Kozuki Clan!
As none other than Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Lord Momonosuke is in danger!
Oh. I seem to remember hearing a voice from somewhere earlier...
saying that Lord Momonosuke is with a kunoichi...
That must be Shinobu!
Which means we can contact him!
It's rather uncouth to chase down a dying man.
The Red Scabbards samurai will meet their demise here. having achieved nothing!
Myself included...
Let's go out with a bang, shall we?
You guys!
You are my friends, are you not?
XY
**
Ashura!
Get out of here. you guys!
/1 Go and stop Kanjuro!
//
What are you doing?!
Get off of me!
Save Lord Momonosuke for me!
We are in your debt. Ashura!
You bastard!
How dare you get in my way?!
) ull 111/ 111
Damn you! Get off of me!
You will never defile the memory of Kozuki Oden ever again!
Kanjuro!
It's finally time for me, the star of the show, to take center stage!
I!  then. ! eliminate the Kozuki..
and finally. I die!
This will be my grand finale!
My life is one big. beautiful play!
HH
Jack!
/You bastard! Back for round two?!
What a pain in the ass.
These weaklings tried to stand in my way...
all to protect their precious kings!
Cat! Raizo! All of you. go on ahead!
Everyone, save Lord Momonosuke for me!
Let's go, Kin.
Yeah...
Be sure to catch up to us, Inuarashi! We shall await your arrival!
////
1 //// Do you intend to fight me all on your own, Ruler of the Day?
We're both injured.
Seems like a fair fight.
I didn't stay behind to settle an old grudge.
If I let you run free, more people will get hurt! And I can't allow that. Jack!
There's no view of the moon from here!
There's no poison gas, either!
Well. then... Let's find out who fate favors today.
Hurry up and put it out!
Water! We need more water!
It's you..!
It's time to teach you fools a lesson.
I thought you were dead...
How did you survive?!
How could Kaido betray me like that?!
There is no doubt about it. Lord Orochi..
You were certainly beheaded by Kaido... once, that is.
However...
I'm gonna burn it all down!
Onigashima will be a raging inferno by the time I'm through with it!
There's nowhere to run in the air.
All you can do is die!
I'll kill every last one of them!
They'll rue the day they crossed me!
Momonosuke!
Can you go back to normal?
You stick out like a sore thumb.
Sure...
11. Stay put this time, Momonosuke! z
1/11 14 My apologies...
/1
It may not look it. but I have learned to control it better...
When I first met Luffy and the others.
I would turn into a dragon every time I got surprised or felt sad.
Astonishing.
I wonder if it's like my father's power...
If I could turn into a monster like he does. I would be of some help to everyone...
M Luffy is still fighting Kaido, right?
I wonder if he's okay!
I wanna take down Kaido too! As Oden!
1//1 Luffy is growing much weaker...
but somehow, he is in good spirits!
Thank goodness...
What?!
How can you tell. Lord Momonosuke?!
How do we beat these guys?
They shrug off every attack we throw at them...!
That's a couple of Emperors for you.. They've got some thick skin.
Can't they at least pretend it's making a dent?!
It is working!
After a beating like that, there's no way they're not hurting!
They're humans just like us!
Gum-Gum...
11, 1/
You already tried that earlier! Think before you dive in!
How can you call them human...
when the gap between us is so big?
Look, if you don't think we can win. then why are you here?
// We're trying to figure out how to win!
We should lure one of them away from here.
Good idea.
With the two of them side by side like this...
it looks like we're in hell.
Hell, huh?
I've been there plenty of times.
That light in your eyes never goes out...
Straw Hat!
We have the upper hand!
TO BE CONTINUED